export const Grammar1 = [
  {
    question: "Sherry’s mother asked _____not to open the door for strangers.",
    Options: ["Him", "Her", "Someone", "Anyone"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "_____is a demonstrative pronoun?",
    Options: ["Each other", "Myself", "It", "This"],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "‘You are my best friend’ - Which one is the subject pronoun?",
    Options: ["My", "Are", "You", "Friend"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "‘My baby dropped her hanky on the ground’- Which one is the possessive pronoun?",
    Options: ["My", "Her", "The", "On"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "‘You must trust yourself’ – Which one is a reflexive pronoun?",
    Options: ["You", "Must", "Yourself", "None of the above"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "The pronouns (I and We) which denote a person of speaking is said to be personnel pronouns of the ______.",
    Options: ["First Person", "Second Person", "Third Person", "None of these"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "The plural form of personal pronoun (my) is:",
    Options: ["we", "me", "our", "us"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "This, That, Those, These etc are called _______.",
    Options: ["Personal Pronouns", "Demonstrative Pronouns", "Interrogative Pronouns", "Distributive Pronouns"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "This book is mine. The underlined word is ______ pronoun.",
    Options: ["Nominative", "Possessive", "Accusative", "Both A and C"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "The pronoun of third-person has ______ genders.",
    Options: ["Two", "Three", "Four", "Five"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  }
];
